Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
♪ Tell me I'm a setback ♪
♪ Tell me that I'm bad for you ♪
♪ Say we had a good game ♪
♪ But someone had to lose ♪
♪ I think we took a wrong turn ♪
♪ Somewhere along the way ♪
♪ So now I'll take a step back ♪
♪ So you can have your space ♪
♪ You said you loved me regardless ♪
♪ Now look at the problems you started ♪
♪ In love with a struggling artist ♪
♪ I wasn't what you really wanted… ♪
Ready, go, hut!
♪ Pastime that you can't let go of ♪
♪ Go of ♪
-♪ Well, maybe I'm a landmine… ♪
-[whistle blows]
Newsome! What the hell happened?
Sorry, Coach, I misread the coverage.
We're 0-4. Maybe act like
you've seen a football before.
Hey, Coach, should I start warming up?
-No.
Oh, look, hey, I got a call
with the superintendent in five minutes,
so just keep having them do long passes
until our QB successfully completes one!
-[boy] You be running sprints!
-Copy that.
Glad to have you.
[indistinct chatter]
All right, look alive, gentlemen.
Here comes Coach Walter.
So, you and Allen finally ready
to let me run the ball, or…
No. Zebra 34!
[Dylan] Another passing play?
Come on, man.
Not trying to wear out my arm
during a bye week.
Looks like you're not trying at all
from where we're standing.
Come on. You've been consistently
off target, missing receivers.
You threw three picks last week.
You don't seem to care.
You know, you're worse than my dad,
riding me like this. I care.
Then prove it.
Work on your passing.
Zebra 34!
[whistle blows]
All right, boys, let's go.
You heard Coach. Ready!
-[boys] Zebra 34.
-[boy] Zebra 34.
[boy 2] All right, boys.
-[chuckles] Watch this.
-[boy] Watch Mike! Watch Mike!
Ready!
[boy 2] Hey, fix that jersey.
-Down, set, hut!
-[boy] Here we go.
[rock music playing]
[indistinct yelling]
[boy] Goddamn!
[boy 2] I'm on him! On him!
[Dylan] Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Let's go, baby.
-[whistle blows]
-[boy] Come on.
Hey, just gotta let me do me, Coach!
Whoo!
-Hey!
-[boy] Come on!
[boy 2] Not even 34.
You realize we could save time
and avoid carpal tunnel
by whipping these up in Photoshop?
Yes, but there's just something
about doing it by hand.
Reminds me of this little thrift shop
in Greenpoint Lucy loved.
I can always get down
with an arts and crafts sesh.
Thanks, Danny.
[phone dings]
How did Cole take the news
about you and Erin?
I haven't had the opportunity to tell him.
You guys share a room.
[Danny] What am I supposed to say?
"Good night, sleep tight."
"Oh, hope you don't mind
I'm dating your ex."
The longer you drag this out,
the more likely he finds out
in some other less ideal way.
I'm gonna do it.
Tonight.
Good. You got this.
[phone ringing]
Go ahead. Tell Erin I said hi.
Oh, nope, no. [chuckles]
No taking out Gregory Peck
until you finish your homework.
Maybe he could help?
Oh, nice try, but I wasn't born yesterday.
-Hey, Mom?
-Yeah?
I need to take cookies
to the game this weekend.
-Ooh. Do you wanna bake 'em with me later?
-Yeah.
-Chocolate chip or oatmeal?
-Both.
Hey, Jordan, how was your day?
Better before this conversation.
-[Katherine] Hi.
-Hi.
Are you all ready for the pop-up tomorrow?
Almost,
but honestly, I'm still holding out
for a few more donations.
We had to toss a box because someone
thought it was a trash can.
-It was so gross.
-How much are you trying to raise again?
A thousand dollars.
You're welcome to dig through
my old stuff in your closet.
Really?
Of course. Take whatever you want.
Just don't judge me
for my past fashion crimes.
Exactly how bad are we talking here?
Have you heard of the band Wham!?
[Jackie chuckles]
[country music playing on radio]
I'm telling you, Gracie,
this whole guest ranch business
is making me nervous.
I mean, it's a bunch of yurts, Mom.
It's a bunch of yurts for now.
But before long,
we're gonna be the next Telluride or Aspen
with hotels and chains
and celebrity vacation homes.
I mean, does that sound appealing to you?
Maybe if it's the right celebrity.
I mean, if Timothée Chalamet
wants to vacation here,
I'll personally roll out the red carpet.
Oh, it's all fun and games, honey.
Until we can't afford
to live here anymore.
[Alex] So have I gotten better?
[indistinct chatter]
-[Katherine] Hi, Grace.
-[Grace] Hey.
-Jackie's upstairs.
-[Grace] Okay, thank you.
-Hi.
-[Joanne] Hi.
Thank you for having her over for dinner.
Bob's working late,
and I have a… [clears throat]
I have a thing.
-Oh, she's welcome anytime. You know that.
-Okay.
So, how have you been?
I have been… okay.
Just catching up on work stuff.
Mm.
Look, I'm gonna put us out of our misery
before we start talking about the weather.
[sighs]
Jo, you were
the first person I met in Silver Falls
whose last name wasn't Walter.
And I'm gonna do everything in my power
to make sure that this business
doesn't encroach on
anybody's peace of mind,
but… I would really hate
for it to come between us.
Me too.
So we won't let it.
-Okay?
-[Katherine] Okay.
-I'll see you at book club. Okay.
-Yep.
I have a lot to say about chapter five.
[laughs]
-[engine starts]
-[sighs]
All right, Murph. We break our record,
there might be some treats in your future.
Huh?
[Blake] Last ride.
Plant your boots, tip your hat,
and let's kick dust.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Alex] There we go.
-[horse neighs softly]
[Alex] Come on, Murph.
[Blake] And…
time.
-Okay.
-I'm impressed.
Yeah?
Impressed you didn't fall off,
'cause you were looking a little unsteady.
But if we shorten your stirrups
and work on your core, then,
you'll get there.
And our time?
Shaved off two seconds.
It's a new personal best.
Okay. Could've led with that.
I could've,
but it's also my job to keep you humble.
[Alex chuckles]
-[Blake] Nice work, pal.
-Thanks.
-Oh, I was talking to the horse.
-[horse whinnies]
Oh, she was talking to you. Hear that?
What's the tea on Annie Oakley over there?
Her name's Blake. She's 18,
and she's teaching him how to not die
doing dangerous rodeo stuff.
Are we sure that's all she's teaching him?
I don't know, and I don't care.
He wanted space, so he's getting it.
Holy shoulder pads, Batman!
Like, can I borrow that?
Only if you promise to lose it.
What are those?
They're my mom's.
They're her designs.
[emotional music playing]
[Dylan] Ten!
[exhales] Hoo!
All right, boys, don't forget.
Kegger at my place tonight, all right?
Invite only.
What about your dad?
Oh, if it doesn't affect my QB rating
or our record,
he doesn't give a damn what I do.
Plus, he's in Denver
with his new flavor of the week anyways.
Hey, boys,
could you give us space for a sec?
[Dylan scoffs]
Sup, coach?
You know what's up.
You ignored my play call out there today.
Relax, bro. I was just having some fun.
Have fun on your own time, okay?
When Coach isn't out there, I'm in charge.
Yeah, but, um,
you're not really in charge, are you?
What's your problem, huh?
I thought you were happy
to have me back on the team.
That was before I knew
you'd end up being Allen's little bitch.
So, you're telling me you didn't know
you had ten designer dresses
just chilling in your closet?
Honestly, I mean, the days
before moving here were such a blur.
People coming and going, boxes everywhere.
I guess they got loaded up
with my things by mistake.
Well, maybe we could sell a few
at the pop-up.
I mean, I'm sure they'd go faster
than Mrs. Sapp's banana pudding
at a church potluck.
[emotional music playing]
Oh my gosh.
Oh my… Don't listen to me.
Sorry. I didn't even think about--
No, I mean, you're right.
Even with these last-minute donations,
we're still light on merchandise.
Selling the dresses makes sense.
Yeah… Hey, never mind.
[chuckles] It's okay.
If we have to sacrifice a photo booth
and ask Andrew Neville
from AP Euro to DJ, then so be it.
It'll be great. Okay?
Ho! Ho! Ho! Ho!
-What are you doing?
-Mr. Walter okayed the demo.
-That would be me. I'm Mr. Walter.
The one in charge.
The…
Okay, just… Do not touch this shed. Okay?
There's nothing you can do
to expedite the process?
[man] No, not unless you have friends
at municipal planning.
No. No, I don't.
[man] Hey, well, the good news is that
the construction permits were approved.
As soon as that shed's firewood,
Richard wants us to start digging trenches
for the new utility line.
-All right.
-Hey, Derren, it's George.
I need to talk to my kid
for a minute, all right?
-[Derren] Yeah. Sure thing, George.
-Thank you.
I'll call back.
[phone beeps]
What's up?
I just stopped a bulldozer
from tearing down the shed.
You know anything about that?
Dad, it's old.
It's got a hole in the roof,
and we need utilities for our guests.
You do not make decisions about my ranch
without talking to me first.
Look, I am really trying to support
your vision and not micromanage this,
but your great-great-grandfather
built that shed, all right?
And I have memories there, so…
Look, can't we just trench around it
and put the utilities on the other side?
No, I--
Okay, then move it. Move the shed. Put it…
Put it out where the silo used to be.
Moving it would be twice as expensive
as demolishing it, and--
-[phone ringing]
-Hang on.
I should take this.
Hey, Marlee,
thanks for getting back to me.
Yeah. Question for you.
Is your brother Pat still
at Colorado Parks and Wildlife?
[Dylan] Hey!
Cool if I sit?
It's a free country.
[Dylan] All right.
[sighs]
Best view in town, am I right?
I like it better when it's quiet.
You know, sometimes I come up here
and just… imagine
what's happening
in those houses down there.
Like the one with the red roof?
Yeah, they're probably
sleeping off a rager.
[chuckles]
Or over there?
You know, I bet you a second-grader is
defending his property from two burglars
after his family left on vacation.
-That's the plot of Home Alone.
-Gotcha.
[chuckles] See,
I knew you weren't ignoring me.
Did you bet that you could
make me popular or something?
No, I--
Because honestly, I have no desire
to act out that '90s rom-com.
Ouch. [chuckles]
Tell me how you really feel. [chuckles]
Oh, I'm late for my shift.
You really are all work and no play, huh?
Yeah, well, not everyone
has the luxury to play.
Hey, uh, so I was thinking, uh,
these obstacle courses are cool and all,
but maybe we can start scouting
broncs for me to take on?
I mean, it's not like
I haven't done it before, right?
Right, and how did that work out?
You got bucked off and roughed up,
which brought you to me.
Look, Alex,
seriously, you've made some real progress,
but you can't rush this.
Every ride could be your last. Got it?
Mm.
Tomorrow, I figured
we'd take a field trip,
scope out your competition.
You know, unless you've got
something better to do.
I'm all yours.
[uplifting music playing]
[Will] You're a lifesaver, Pat. Thank you.
-[Pat] No problem. Talk to you later.
-Bye.
Did you lose the keys
to your place or something?
No. No, it just got
too quiet there without Hayley.
You must miss her a lot.
Yeah, but this semester abroad,
it's an incredible opportunity for her.
She needs me to be supportive,
so I'm trying.
Hey, Will, go easy on Dad, huh?
He's trying too.
[somber music playing]
-You ready, champ?
-I've been ready for this my whole life.
You want to talk about it?
About?
The reason you're home
on a Friday night watching Rudy.
Hey, Rudy's a classic.
Yeah, a classic that you only watch
after you've had a bad practice.
Well, I'm more interested in talking about
whatever it is you've been up to.
Where you been all gussied up?
Oh, um, Amy had a few of us over
for some birthday cake and karaoke.
Amy who?
Amy from drama club.
Sounds fun.
For sure.
[movie on TV resumes]
[gentle music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, I was hoping we could go over
the schedule for driving lessons.
Wow.
I remember that collection.
Vogue called it,
"Effortlessly simple
contemporary glamour."
[chuckles] Jewels by Angelica Howard.
[Katherine] So, what's going on?
Grace suggested that we take
a few to the pop-up.
Oh.
Well, what do you think?
I made a list of pros and cons.
And all of the reasons
why I should are valid.
But I don't… I don't know.
You know nobody would blame you
if you wanted to keep them.
They're not just ordinary dresses.
They're your mom's art.
Art that's meant to be worn,
not packed away in boxes.
You know, way before your mom
started dressing all those celebrities,
she would dress all of us
for all kinds of things.
My junior year,
I was dating this guy, Brian something.
And I remember one day he called me up
and was like, "We need to talk."
So… [scoffs]
…obviously I knew it was over.
So what's your mom do?
She drags me out shopping,
and she makes me buy this dress.
I mean, talk about revenge dressing.
She was all about making sure
that I felt bulletproof.
"Fashion is the armor
to survive the reality of everyday life."
It's a Bill Cunningham quote
she had on her desk.
You know, Jackie, whatever decision
you make is the right one.
And you're 100% sure
you don't want any of this stuff?
Positive.
Who knows? Maybe it'll be the armor
that somebody else needs.
♪ When we were kids ♪
♪ We were running around
With nothing else to do ♪
♪ When we were kids… ♪
So as we still need a feature
for the "Here's What's Happening
in Silver Falls" section,
I thought it's worth spotlighting
last week's town hall.
People aren't exactly thrilled
with the idea
of opening Silver Falls up to tourism.
I don't know.
[chuckles]
Do you really think high schoolers care
about what's happening
in my family's ranch?
I mean, it's a significant development
that could affect the entire community.
Okay, let's move on
to pop-up coverage, shall we?
Zach's handling photography, obviously.
Nate, it's your byline,
but since you're pulling
double duty as DJ,
which Student Council greatly appreciates,
I'm happy to help gather
diverse perspectives,
quotes, et cetera, on the core issue
behind the pop-up. Budget cuts.
Yeah, okay.
I'm also gonna talk to Mr. Duffy
about the marching band
not getting the new uniforms
they were promised this year
and Ms. Hampton about withdrawing from
the math Olympiad because of travel costs.
But I mean, hey, as long as school sports
is thriving, it's all good, right?
[Skylar] Exactly.
This isn't the time for a puff piece.
Don't hold back.
♪ Don't hold back ♪
♪ I want to break free
'Cause it's singing through your body ♪
♪ And I'm carried by the sound ♪
Of course you know Perfume Genius.
I mean, it's not exactly
as obscure as Trash Dolls, so…
And are these bands?
-Well…
-Perfume Genius is one guy.
But Trash Dolls is a band.
As you can see, Zach,
I'd be lost musically without this one.
You're welcome.
[chuckles]
Mm.
I think I need a refill. Anyone else?
-Nope.
-No, thanks.
[Nathan] Hmm.
[scoffs] I think someone's got
a little crush on you.
No. [chuckles]
We… we like similar music and…
Hey, even if he… even if he did,
I'm happily taken.
Damn right you are.
-[Nathan] Mm-hmm.
-[Skylar chuckles]
[footsteps approaching]
[Jackie] Alex!
I could've seriously hurt you.
You know,
you're getting pretty good at that.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you grew up on a ranch.
Okay, well,
have a nice ride.
Thanks.
Will do.
Have a nice ride?
[door closes]
What happened to you?
Chores.
Want some coffee?
More like need, desperately.
Hey, um, have you noticed
anything weird about Danny lately?
Uh…
Weird how?
I don't know, like,
did anything happen over the summer?
If you're worried something's up,
why not just ask him?
I don't know. I'm probably
just imagining it or something.
[mysterious music playing]
Easy, there's…
It's just there's hay in your hair.
[upbeat music playing]
Got it.
[door opens]
-[George] Oh, hey, Jackie.
-Hi.
Hey, how you doing?
Great.
Yeah, I hear practice was tricky, huh?
That's one way to put it, yeah.
[George] You want to tell me about it?
I thought… I thought Dylan was
gonna make this easier for me.
But he's undermining me
every chance he gets.
Hmm.
Unless I'm just a lousy coach.
Well, you're not a lousy coach. All right?
Allen offered you this job because
you're a natural-born leader, right?
Nobody knows the game like you.
You're in a new role.
It's gonna take a minute
to get their respect.
It's kinda hard to get respect
and be a leader
when your starting quarterback
refuses to listen to you.
-I don't want to fail at this.
-Well, you keep being you.
All right? Trust your instincts.
It'll get through.
Okay, team. How are we looking?
To put it lightly, bleak.
Super helpful, Olivia. Thank you.
I'm just pointing out the obvious.
We promised people vintage.
It's all giving burn-after-wearing.
I've got two more boxes in my car.
Let me guess. More treasures
from the church lost and found?
Funny, but no. Actually, Jackie sent me
over with some old stuff of Katherine's.
Hold on, where is Jackie?
Hi. I brought reinforcements.
Now this is more like it!
No way those belong to Cole's mom.
Actually, my mom designed these.
Jackie, I can't believe you brought them.
[door opens]
-Hi, babe.
-Hmm.
That bulldozer hasn't moved
since yesterday,
so I think you can end your watch.
Or they're just waiting for me
to let my guard down.
[Katherine chuckles]
Oh.
Where are you off to?
I gotta go to the clinic, and then
I'm gonna meet Lori for a drink later.
-Nice.
-And I think I might stop by the pop-up.
And just make sure Jackie's okay.
Well, why wouldn't she be okay?
Apparently, she decided to take
Angelica's dresses after all.
Oh, well, I mean, that's progress, right?
[Katherine] Maybe.
[footsteps approaching]
-Or maybe not. I don't know.
-Well, we'll see.
-Hey, Mom.
-Hi, honey.
How are you?
Good. Dad?
William.
I was thinking we could go fly-fishing.
-[George] Hmm.
-[Will] Today.
Uh… no. No, no,
I got some hay bales coming,
and I gotta place a grain order, so…
And we figured you'd say that,
so Lee's gonna take care of the hay bales,
and Danny's on top of the grain order.
[George sighs]
You need a day off.
You both do.
-Please.
-[George sighs]
Well, why not? Sure.
[Katherine] Good.
The ranch isn't going anywhere.
["In Between Days" playing]
♪ Yesterday I got so old ♪
♪ I felt like I could die ♪
♪ It made me want to cry ♪
♪ Go on, go on, just walk away ♪
♪ Go on, go on, your choice is made ♪
♪ Go on, go on, and disappear ♪
♪ Go on, go on, away from here ♪
♪ And I know I was wrong
When I said it was true ♪
♪ That it couldn't be me ♪
♪ And be her in between ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ Without you… ♪
[Grace] Kiley!
You should get one. For the dance.
School dances are against my religion…
and my work schedule.
-♪ Yesterday I got so scared… ♪
-[phone ringing]
Duty calls.
[overlapping chatter]
♪ Yesterday away from you ♪
♪ It froze me deep inside… ♪
Okay, here you go.
♪ Come back, come back
Don't walk away… ♪
Is everything okay over here?
Yeah. Thank you
for supporting SFH Student Council.
♪ Come back, come back, come back to me… ♪
Jackie,
I know you don't want
or need my two cents,
but I'm giving it anyway, okay?
I think donating those dresses
was really brave.
Why? They're just things.
♪ Without you ♪
Hey, you need a hand?
I've got it.
What are we doing here, Will?
'Cause you hate fly-fishing.
Are you really on board
with this guest ranch idea?
'Cause lately it's like
we're not on the same page, Dad.
First with the town hall,
then with the shed. I mean…
I'm on board, I promise you.
It's just…
I don't want to wake up one morning
and not even recognize my own backyard.
And you think I want that?
It's not you that I'm worried about.
Look, I like Richard well enough.
Like, he's Jackie's uncle,
but doesn't mean
I trust him with our ranch.
Then trust me.
I do.
I'm sorry if I've acted like I didn't.
Thanks for saying that.
Okay.
Show me what I'm doing wrong, please.
Well, for starters…
everything, Will. [laughs]
Okay, hey, look.
Okay, pinch the line. Start with that.
-Okay. All right.
-You gotta control the line.
["Connection" playing]
I know what you're doing.
Shooting the pop-up for the paper?
That's not all you're doing.
I'm just documenting
like any good journalist would.
♪ Riding on any wave ♪
♪ That is the luck you crave ♪
♪ They don't believe it now ♪
♪ They just think it's stupid ♪
♪So, got anything? ♪
♪ Anyone could've done ♪
♪ Who woul'dve cared at all? ♪
♪ Not you ♪
♪ Another heart ♪
♪ Has made the trade ♪
♪ Forget it ♪
♪ Forget it, forget it ♪
♪ I don't understand
How a heart is a spade… ♪
[Ruby] Cole!
♪ But somehow
A vital connection is made… ♪
What do you think?
[sighs]
Very nice.
Where were you last night?
-What was last night?
-Dylan invited the whole team over?
Oh.
If it makes you feel any better,
you didn't miss anything.
I'm sure.
Hey! Isn't this the coolest?
Skylar just spoke to Mato,
and he's super happy with everything.
We might actually pull this off.
Oh no.
Um…
Hey! What the hell is wrong with you?
-Relax.
-Do not tell me to relax, Ruby.
Hey, Jackie, it's not that big a deal.
If the dress were supposed to have a slit,
it would have come with one.
Maybe if you cared about them so much,
you should've left them at home.
Okay, maybe let's not do this
in front of the people we're counting on
to fund our dance.
Ruby, go take that off!
You broke it, you buy it.
Nathan, music.
-Jackie…
-I'm taking a walk.
Cole, let her go.
She needs a minute.
[sighs]
[Katherine] Jackie?
Jackie.
Is everything okay?
Just needed some fresh air.
[Katherine] Hmm.
Got a little, uh, stuffy in there?
Yeah. [chuckles]
One of the girls tore
one of my mom's dresses.
She tore an Angelica Howard original?
She wanted a slit.
[Katherine scoffs]
Okay.
What's her name?
'Cause I'm gonna go in there,
rip that dress out of her hands,
and I'm gonna take it home and fix it.
It's okay. [chuckles]
I guess I just wasn't expecting it
to be so hard to let them go.
Do you want to go home?
I'll be fine. I just… I need a minute.
And a hug?
Yeah.
[emotional music playing]
[horn blows]
[upbeat country music playing]
Okay, that's Wylder Holt.
He's a rising star
among bronc riders under 25
and the reason why we're here.
So pay attention.
-[Wylder] Okay!
-[energetic music playing]
[horn blows]
I give it 80 out of 100.
Oh, tough critic.
[music ends]
Hi, Wylder.
-It's been a minute.
-Blake Hartford.
It has indeed. Who's your friend?
Wylder Holt, Alex Walter.
Alex here is chasing the adrenaline rush.
Well, if anyone can whip you
into bucking shape, Blake's your gal.
Bronc riding's in her blood.
Yeah. My daddy still
would've preferred a son, though.
Hartford, you have more cojones
than half the guys on our circuit.
I wish I could stay and hang,
but we're due in Vegas tomorrow
bright and early.
Don't be a stranger, yeah?
Hope to meet you
in the arena one day, Alex Walter.
See? I know my shit.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-[Blake chuckles]
Just like I know there's one thing
holding Wylder back from true greatness.
Any guesses, class?
-He fights the ride instead of joining it.
-Bingo.
Just hanging on
doesn't make a real cowboy.
It's about connecting,
like you do with Murphy.
Do this right, and soon enough
Wylder will be chasing your dust,
not vice versa.
But we should probably
be getting you home.
Or maybe we don't
have to call it a night just yet.
Aren't you training early?
Word on the street,
your coach is a hard-ass.
Nothing I can't handle.
Okay.
Lead the way.
Alex Walter.
[chuckles]
[country music playing on radio]
♪ Turn the radio up
Sing along to the song-- ♪
Hey, Will.
Let's, um… let's do this again, huh?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Next time it doesn't
have to be something you hate.
[scoffs]
[horse whinnies]
I couldn't remember the exact location
of the old silo, so hopefully this works.
Dad,
the ranch, its history,
they're important to me too.
I want this to work because I care.
Sometimes about the wrong things, but
I'll do better.
We both will.
♪ I pace ♪
♪ I run my mouth ♪
♪ I pray and wait ♪
♪ I cross out his name on the page ♪
♪ How long till this washes away? ♪
♪ How long till ♪
♪ My body is safe? ♪
♪ I walk in the light? ♪
♪ How long till ♪
♪ This heart isn't mine? ♪
♪ The rise and fall of his chest on me ♪
♪ I'm trying, but still it's all I see… ♪
-Oh. Hi.
-Oh, hi.
I didn't hear you come in.
Yeah, I ran in here
to get a head start on my article.
Great.
-So, how'd the pop-up go?
-You know, I'd say it was a success.
When I left, most of the racks were empty.
Jackie's dresses were gone.
Oh.
♪ I promise every day to change… ♪
[Katherine] Nice photo.
Looks like you caught someone's eye.
Cutie.
♪ How long till ♪
♪ My body is safe? ♪
♪ I walk in the light? ♪
We could offer a journey through time
on horseback, you know,
showcasing the barn,
the shed, the cider cart,
that creek where Amos Walter struck gold.
Let's make our family history
a living part of the business, you know?
Will, I love that idea. It's great.
But Amos Walter struck pyrite.
[Will chuckles]
Yeah, but, "Come see
where Amos Walter found fool's gold"
doesn't have the same ring.
Oh, good!
-[George] Oh, hey!
-I can call off the search party.
[chuckles] Sorry.
We stopped to get a bite to eat.
Mission accomplished.
-[door opens]
-[Richard] Anyone home?
[door closes]
Richard. Hey, what are you doing here?
Is this about Jackie?
Uh…
Not exactly.
-Look, there's no easy way to say this.
-[George] So just say it.
Okay.
I'm here 'cause you bungled the town hall,
and we can't allow this community
to delay breaking ground any further.
We don't have the time
or the money to play games.
How'd you hear about town hall?
Keeping tabs on us?
Because I called him.
[tense music playing]
So, what's the verdict?
Well, with our cut of the pizza sales,
plus clothes,
we made over $200 more than our goal.
Okay.
I have to admit,
you do have some good ideas. Sometimes.
I am gonna need that in writing.
Um, about earlier, I know
I shouldn't have blown up like that.
Don't apologize.
I meant what I said.
Donating those dresses was really brave.
That kind of bravery
deserves to be rewarded.
I thought…
Erin, you set this aside for me?
I know that if I found
something of my dad's,
I… never want to let it go.
Besides, it's totally you.
Now you have the perfect dress
to wear to the dance that you saved.
[Alex sighs]
[sighs]
Hey, Kiley.
I'll give you a few minutes.
I'm headed out,
if you want to roll with me.
Friends give friends rides home sometimes.
But you can ride in the back seat.
Pretend to be a chauffeur
if it makes you feel more comfortable.
[pensive music playing]
[Alex] All right.
Do you have any of these things?
Ready when you are.
I was so close to just ripping off
the band-aid last night, but…
he was watching Rudy.
And he only really--
He only watches Rudy
when he's had a bad practice.
-Yeah.
-I know.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
We shouldn't have to drive
one town over to go catch a movie.
I mean, I would like
to go to the dance with my boyfriend.
I'm your boyfriend?
I mean,
yeah.
If that's okay.
Congrats on another successful fundraiser,
New York.
You good?
Ask me tomorrow.
What?
♪ I don't feel happy ♪
♪ I don't feel sad… ♪
Oh, Danny.
♪ If things are bad ♪
You knew?
♪ Whatever happens ♪
♪ I won't be mad ♪
♪ I'm just so numb ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ So I don't feel nothing ♪
♪ You see when I'm bluffing ♪
♪ I say that I'm good ♪
♪ But the truth of it is
That reality's crushing me ♪
♪ So if you ever see the real me ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Where he's hiding, no you won't see ♪
♪ Hey♪
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ We're past that now
We're past that now ♪
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org